learnesl.net 2016-12-26

# Privacy Policy - Learn ESL

**Learnesl Privacy Policy**   
We at Learnesl.net understand that your privacy is extremely important. We value your privacy and we will do everything possible to keep your information private. For each visitors, our server automatically recognize the IP address only. We don not automatically detect or collect name, email addresses, or any other personal information. Every lesson without book is provide at free of charge. Learnesl.net does not require signing up, logging in, or registering to study or access any lessons.   
We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to a newsletter or enter information on our site. When ordering or registering on our site as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with experience. Your email address is NOT sold or shared with anyone outside of Learnesl.net.

###  **Advertisers**

 **Google Adsense**   
Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Privacy Policy.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

 **Contact Us**  
If there are any questions regarding the privacy policy you may contact us using the [contact form.](http://www.learnesl.net/contact-us/) This privacy policy may change from time to time. We will inform you by email in case of any important changes of our privacy policy.
